[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Is that your message?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "We are reassessing and re-evaluating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "But are you staying in the race?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "We are re-evaluating and reassessing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "How soon until we have a final answer on your future plans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "We'll be making a decision in the next several days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Is he toast?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, it's hard for me to know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Do you feel sympathy for him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, I don't know about sympathy at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Never mind Washington but to the electorate as they used to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Well, probably not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What do you make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, I guess you could compare it to many others that have done this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "I mean if this has the desired effect on the global economy and impacts favorably on jobs, is Barack Obama sitting pretty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, time will tell.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Senator, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "What are you going to do to save the day for your campaign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "I love this preoccupation with national polls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Karen"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "What do you think of Herman Cain's crisis that he's in, where he's being hit with this slew of sexual allegations?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "ANTORUM: Well, what Karen and I do in all of these races is we pray for all of the folks who have to go through this very difficult process.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "How's it been for you in particular living with this and having to run for president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "It's very difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandusky"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "I suppose the obvious question, why did your client keep his silence all these years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I think that a fair question and I think it really requires us to really understand how sexual abuse by authority figures like Sandusky coerced silence and secrecy and shame, and cause this survivor and other victims like him to really believe that they're being cared for and to believe that it's their fault.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "I mean what does your client feel when he hears that Jerry is just a big old kid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Well, what he feels and what every survivor feels when they hear that kind of denial and minimization is fury, because there is a tendency of people like we just heard to want to believe the most powerful and effective among us like Jerry Sandusky wouldn't do something like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "And what should happen to it now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, what I feel is important as what we need to really do and the question we need to ask first is why did Jerry Sandusky for as long as he did be allowed to do what he did for decades to so many kids while so many people around him saw the signs or got the reports and did nothing, and chose instead to protect him and the institution.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Why are you doing it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Well, I think a lot of mistruths have been written about Phoebe and I think that it was time to take her back to reclaim her as ours and to put an end to some of the stories that have been going around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Were you taken back by the kind of worldwide attention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Very much so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "What was -- what was the motivation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "'BRIEN: I was taking a career break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "How they would adapt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "No, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What kind of girl was she, Phoebe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Extraordinarily intelligent and vivacious and great sense of humor.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Was she a confident girl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "In ways, she was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "The reason I ask is I think crucially to how this all play out, when you enrolled Phoebe at the school, you did tell the officials that she was susceptible to bullying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What had happened before that made you feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Phoebe, she had -- she had a run in with some girls before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "In Ireland?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ireland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What did they say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Oh, that will be no problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "And one of the vice principals was called on a personal call and asked to keep an eye out for Phoebe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "So they knew.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "When did you discover for the first time that Phoebe was being bullied?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "November.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["December"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "What could you deduce?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, once, in December, she told me that one of the girls involved in a new incident of bullying kept coming up to her in the hallways and screaming at her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Did you know that these girls were using social media like Facebook and so on to bully her as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "TO", "RB", "PRP$", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "But she wasn't -- the bullying on Facebook, the cyber bullying that has been put out by people, was just a small component of the bullying of Phoebe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "This is a systematic abuse of somebody, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Oh, yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "``", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "''", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "To drive somebody to suicide and they just but \"done\" on Facebook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "``", "NN", "''", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Or \"she got what she deserved,\" that was another one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Why were they so determined to force Phoebe into what eventually happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I -- I honestly don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "It's wicked, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "It's -- it's astounding that there was never a stop mechanism, you know, internal stop mechanism for some of these kids, to say this is going too far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "What is your reaction when you see again Guy Sayer saying that so soon after Phoebe died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "It was -- it was very painful because, you know, you realize as a parent that no matter what I did, no matter how many times I called the school, no matter how many people I might have spoken to there, that she didn't stand a chance there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sayer", "Phoebe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "And as a mother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "As a mother, I think that had the school intervened the way they should have intervened, if they had followed up the way they should have followed up, that Phoebe would still be here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Do you feel that justice was done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I'd like to actually clarify, because I know that there are some journalist that think that prison terms were on the cards.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Has she ever said anything to you, Sharon Velazquez?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon Velazquez"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Nothing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Never wrote to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Did any of them write to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Did you feel that remorse was sincere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Did you pick up on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "WDT", "NN", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What have been the implications of that for future cases now involving bullying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, they were tried as youthful offenders, those that fit our -- that were under the age of 17.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "In simple terms, what that is law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Essentially what it does is mandate the schools to report incidences of bullying, should they believe that that -- an act is one of bullying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What would you like the legacy to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Well, ideally, I would like it to be that humans just treat each other in a civilized manner and no boundaries.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "You're not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "No I -- no, I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "And actually if the legacy is that, in future, schools are just more aware, they take more action earlier, and some lives can be saved rather than lost, because of what's happened, that is at least a positive that comes out of this hell for you, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "NN", "RBR", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "VBN", ",", "IN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]